Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 10 and District 10 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE National Office Records Relating to District 10 and District 10 Locals
1936-1994
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
UE.4.1.10
6 Linear Feet (5 boxes)
This series contains files on United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) District 10 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Scope and Content Notes
District 10 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) included locals in Arizona, California, Utah and Washington, which are now part of the UE's Western Region. This series contains files on UE District 10 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts. Most of the correspondence is between UE national officers and district or local officers.
Previous Citation
UE National Office Records Relating to District 10 and District 10 Locals, 1936-1994, UE.4.1.10, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Arrangement
This series has been arranged into two subseries. The first contains records pertaining to District 10. The other subseries contains records pertaining to specific locals within the district, and are further arranged numerically by local number into sections.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America in 1975, 1986, 1997, and 2001.
Related Material
UE District 10 Records, 1950s-1970s, UE.15.10, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 1014 Records, 1990s, UE.16.1014, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 1015 Records, 1970s, UE.16.1015, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 1421 Records, 1980s-1990s, UE.16.1421, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Labor unions -- Washington -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- Utah -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- California -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- Arizona -- History -- 20th century; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- Washington -- History; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- United States -- History; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- Utah -- History; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- Arizona – History; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- California – History; Labor; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. District 10; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; Matles, James J.; Emspak, Julius
- District 10, 1.
  - District 10 Executive Board Minutes, July 16, 1954-April 22, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - District 10 District Council Minutes, May 1, 1937-December 8, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - District 10 District Council Minutes, March 26, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - District 10 District Council Minutes, August 23, 1952-April 23, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - District 10 District Council Minutes, July 16, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - District 10 District Council Resolutions (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - District 10 William Elconin Incoming Correspondence, 1947-1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Julius Emspak to William Elconin Regarding District 10 Organization, November 17, 1950; 1.
    - Albert Fitzgerald to Elconin Regarding Factionalism, March 2, 1948; 2.
    - James Matles to Elconin Regarding Local 1421, January 21, 1949; 3.
    - Russ Nixon to Elconin Regarding PAC, September 8, 1947; 4.
  - District 10 William Elconin Outgoing Correspondence, 1948-1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - William Elconin to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Southern California Conference, February 6, 1948; 1.
    - Elconin to Julius Emspak Regarding Political Action and Southern California Conference, July 1, 1948; 2.
    - Elconin to Emspak Regarding Southern California Conference and Red-baiting, October 4, 1948; 3.
    - Elconin to Fitzgerald Regarding 1948 Congress of Industrial Organizations Convention, December 8, 1948; 4.
    - Elconin to Fitzgerald Regarding 1950 UE Conference and Inter-union Rivalry, March 20, 1950; 5.
    - Elconin to Emspak Regarding District Council and Inter-union Rivalry, November 14, 1950; 6.
    - Elconin to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, District 10, and Organization, November 27, 1950; 7.
    - Elconin to Fitzgerald Regarding District 10 and Factionalism, January 24, 1951; 8.
    - Elconin to Fitzgerald Regarding District 10 Conference, October 13, 1953; 9.
    - Elconin to Fitzgerald Regarding District 10 Conference and West Coast Trip, February 4, 1955; 10.
    - Elconin to All Locals Regarding Mill Town, February 14, 1955; 11.
  - District 10 Robert Shippey Incoming Correspondence, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - James Carey to Robert Shippey Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, August 23, 1937; 1.
    - Carey to Shippey Regarding Organization and Officers, March 11, 1938; 2.
    - Julius Emspak to Shippey Regarding Organization, March 18, 1937; 3.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Organization and Utility Workers, March 23, 1937; 4.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Finances and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, May 17, 1937; 5.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Finances, June 15, 1937; 6.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Finances, July 14, 1937; 7.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Per Capita, July 22, 1937; 8.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Union Label, July 28, 1937; 9.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Per Capita, August 16, 1937; 10.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Per Capita and 1937 UE Convention, August 25, 1937; 11.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Per Capita, September 28, 1937; 12.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Local 1406 Organization, November 20, 1937; 13.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Finances, November 23, 1937; 14.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Per Capita and Organization, November 23, 1937; 15.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Per Capita, December 2, 1937; 16.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Pacific Gas Electric Organization, December 3, 1937; 17.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Local 1406 and Per Capita, December 23, 1937; 18.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Utility Conference, January 28, 1938; 19.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Los Angeles Organization, March 4, 1938; 20.
    - Emspak to Shippey Regarding Per Capita, April 19, 1938; 21.
  - District 10 Robert Shippey Incoming Correspondence, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Victor Levitt to Robert Shippey Regarding Finances, July 10, 1937; 1.
    - Levitt to Shippey Regarding People's Press and Organization, September 17, 1937; 2.
    - James Matles to Shippey Regarding American Meter Negotiations, August 10, 1937; 3.
    - Matles to Shippey Regarding Gerard Hopkins Strike and Local 1219, October 13, 1937; 4.
    - Matles to Shippey Regarding Finances, October 21, 1937; 5.
    - Albert Stonkus to Shippey Regarding West Coast Organization, June 23, 1937; 6.
    - Stonkus to Shippey Regarding Organization and Contracts, July 20, 1937; 7.
    - Stonkus to Shippey Regarding Staff Members and Organization, July 23, 1937; 8.
    - Stonkus to Shippey Regarding Mountain States Power Organization, August 4, 1937; 9.
    - Stonkus to Shippey Regarding Pacific Gas Electric Mountain States Power Organization, August 17, 1937; 10.
    - Stonkus to Shippey Regarding Organization, August 9, 1937; 11.
    - Stonkus to Shippey Regarding Staff Members, August 13, 1937; 12.
    - Stonkus to Shippey Regarding Organization, August 16, 1937; 13.
    - Stonkus to Shippey Regarding Utilities Conference, August 18, 1937; 14.
    - Stonkus to Shippey Regarding People's Press, August 18, 1937; 15.
    - Stonkus to Shippey Regarding Factionalism and Staff Members, September 24, 1937; 16.
  - District 10 Robert Shippey Incoming Correspondence, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Albert Stonkus to Robert Shippey Regarding California Trip, October 22, 1937; 1.
    - Stonkus to Shippey Regarding Finances, December 2, 1937; 2.
    - Unsigned Regarding Staff Members, October 11, 1937; 3.
  - District 10 Robert Shippey Outgoing Correspondence, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Robert Shippey to Julius Emspak Regarding Organization, March 19, 1937; 1.
    - Shippey to James Carey Regarding Local 1425 Organization, March 23, 1937; 2.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, April 22, 1937; 3.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Finances, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, and Organization, May 8, 1937; 4.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 20, 1937; 5.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, May 22, 1937; 6.
    - Shippey to Carey Regarding Staff Members, June 3, 1937; 7.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Organization and Per Capita, June 19, 1937; 8.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Local 1412 Organization and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, June 19, 1937; 9.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Supplies, June 20, 1937; 10.
    - Shippey to Albert Stonkus Regarding Organization and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, July 6, 1937; 11.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Local 1426 Contracts, Union Label, and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry with Wage Rates, July 16, 1937; 12.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, July 19, 1937; 13.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding National Labor Relations Board and White Collar Organization, July 24, 1937; 14.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding American Meter Negotiations, July 30, 1937; 15.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Political Action, Finances, and Organization, July 31, 1937; 16.
  - District 10 Robert Shippey Outgoing Correspondence, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Robert Shippey to Albert Stonkus Regarding Organization, August 1937; 1.
    - Shippey to UE Regarding Per Capita, August 10, 1937; 2.
    - Shippey to Julius Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, August 12, 1937; 3.
    - Shippey to Stonkus Regarding Per Capita, Wages, and Pacific Gas & Electric, August 16, 1937; 4.
    - Shippey to James Carey Regarding Staff Members, August 17, 1937; 5.
    - Shippey to Carey Regarding Staff Members, August 18, 1937; 6.
    - Shippey to James Matles Regarding American Meter Negotiations, August 21, 1937; 7.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, August 22, 1937; 8.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding 1937 UE Convention, August 27, 1937; 9.
    - Shippey to Victor Levitt Regarding International Brotherhood of Teamsters Inter-union Rivalry, September 14, 1937; 10.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, September 19, 1937; 11.
    - Shippey to Stonkus Regarding Staff Members, September 23, 1937; 12-13.
    - Shippey to Stonkus Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism with September 18, 1937, District Council Minutes, September 24, 1937; 14.
    - Shippey to Matles Regarding Staff Members, October 1, 1937; 15.
    - Shippey to Matles Regarding Local 1412 Organization with October 14, 1937, Samuel Horn Letter, October 15, 1937; 16.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, October 16, 1937; 17.
    - Shippey to Stonkus Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, October 16, 1937; 18.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Organization, October 17, 1937; 19.
  - District 10 Robert Shippey Outgoing Correspondence, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Robert Shippey to Albert Stonkus Regarding Pacific Gas & Electric Organization and National Labor Relations Board, October 1937; 1.
    - Shippey to People's Press Regarding Pacific Gas & Electric Organization and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, October 21, 1937; 2.
    - Shippey to Victor Levitt Regarding Pacific Gas & Electrical Organization and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, October 21, 1937; 3.
    - Shippey to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, October 28, 1937; 4.
    - Shippey to Stonkus Regarding Staff Members, Pacific Gas & Electric Organization with November 8, 1937, Letter, November 11, 1937; 5.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Local 1406 Organization, November 13, 1937; 6.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Pacific Gas & Electric Organization, November 20, 1937; 7.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, November 20, 1937; 8.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding District 10 Locals Officers, November 24, 1937; 9.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, November 26, 1937; 10.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Local 1414 Finances, November 30, 1937; 11.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Per Capita Finances, November 30, 1937; 12.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Pacific Gas & Electric Organization, December 7, 1937; 13.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, December 12, 1937; 14.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Pacific Gas & Electric Organization, December 16, 1937; 15.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 14, 1938; 16.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 19, 1938; 17.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Local 1403, January 20, 1938; 18-19.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, February 2, 1938; 20.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, February 14, 1938; 21.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Staff Members and Per Capita, March 9, 1938; 22.
    - Shippey to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Per Capita, April 12, 1938; 23.
    - Shippey to District Council 10 Regarding Per Capita and Factionalism, 1938; 24.
  - District 10 General Incoming Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Janet Barish to Lucia Geiselman Regarding Finances, May 17, 1947; 1.
    - Julius Emspak to Herbert Carlson Regarding GE Oakland Organization, December 23, 1936; 2.
    - Emspak to John Dawe Regarding Western Electric Organization, April 21, 1937; 3.
    - Emspak to F.J. Kane Regarding Organization, August 25, 1937; 4.
    - Emspak to Kane Regarding Western Electric Organization, November 22, 1937; 5.
    - Emspak to Sandra Martin Regarding 1945 UE Convention, July 27, 1945; 6.
    - James Matles to All California Locals Regarding Staff Members, July 20, 1946; 7.
    - David Ratner to Lucia Geiselman Regarding Staff Members, March 25, 1948; 8.
    - Albert Stonkus to Lester Glasson Regarding Staff Members, June 28, 1937; 9.
    - Stonkus to Glasson Regarding Staff Members, June 20, 1937; 10.
    - Stonkus to Glasson Regarding Factionalism, August 13, 1937; 11.
    - Unsigned to Ruth Paull Regarding Finances and Factionalism, December 3, 1947; 12.
  - District 10 General Outgoing Correspondence, 1936-1948 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - John Dawe to UE Regarding Organization, March 15, 1936; 1.
    - Dawe to John Brophy Regarding Western Electric Seattle, February 27, 1937; 2.
    - Dawe to James Carey Regarding Western Electric Seattle Organization, March 24, 1937; 3.
    - Dawe to Carey Regarding Western Electric Seattle Organization, March 29, 1937; 4.
    - Dawe to Julius Emspak Regarding Western Electric Seattle Organization, April 7, 1937; 5.
    - Dawe to Carey Regarding Western Electric Seattle Organization, April 19, 1937; 6.
    - Lucia Geiselman to David Ratner Regarding Finances, May 7, 1947; 7.
    - Geiselman to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, June 11, 1947; 8.
    - Geiselman to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, August 12, 1947; 9.
    - Geiselman to Ratner Regarding Finances, October 9, 1947; 10.
    - Geiselman to Ratner Regarding Finances, January 5, 1948; 11.
    - Geiselman to Ratner Regarding Finances, March 4, 1948; 12.
    - Geiselman to Ratner Regarding Staff Members, March 19, 1948; 13.
    - Geiselman to Ratner Regarding Finances, May 6, 1948; 14.
    - Geiselman to Ratner Regarding Staff Members and Political Action, August 20, 1948; 15.
    - Lester Glasson to Carey Regarding Pacific Gas & Electric Organization, June 1, 1937; 16.
    - Glasson to Stonkus Regarding Pacific Gas & Electric Organization and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, July 2, 1937; 17.
    - Glasson to Victor Levitt Regarding Pacific Gas & Electric Organization, July 12, 1937; 18.
    - Glasson to Stonkus Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, August 13, 1937; 19.
    - Glasson to Carey Regarding Factionalism and Organization, October 5, 1937; 20.
  - District 10 General Outgoing Correspondence, 1937-1953 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - F.J. Kane to Julius Emspak Regarding Western Electric Seattle Organization, May 29, 1937; 1.
    - Kane to Emspak Regarding Western Electric Seattle Organization, August 16, 1937; 2.
    - Kane to Emspak Regarding Western Electric Seattle Organization, October 19, 1937; 3.
    - Kane to James Carey Regarding Western Electric Seattle Organization, November 4, 1937; 4.
    - Kane to Carey Regarding Western Electric Seattle Organization, March 10, 1938; 5.
    - Sylvia Klesan to Albert Stonkus Regarding Finances, November 23, 1937; 6.
    - Walter Turner to Stonkus Regarding Pacific Gas & Electric Organization, August 5, 1937; 7.
    - Turner to Emspak Regarding AFL Inter-union Rivalry, September 9, 1937; 8.
    - Sandra Waite Regarding District Council Meeting, February 2, 1953; 9.
  - District 10 Finances (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Auditor's Report, 1937; 1.
    - Financial Statement, June 1944; 2.
    - Leonard Titelman Organizer's Report, January 15, 1945; 3.
    - Political Action Committee Collection Record, 1944-1947; 4.
  - District 10 Southern California UE News Newspapers, September 30, 1948, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - District 10 Newspapers, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Utility Worker, January 1, 1938; 1.
    - Utility Worker, February 1, 1938; 2.
    - The Industrial Unionist, January 10, 1938; 3.
  - District 10 Pamphlets, 1937-1955 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Statement of Policy Regarding American Meter, 1937; 1.
    - Highlights of the Taft-Hartley Act, 1947; 2.
    - Facts on UE Expulsion, 1949; 3.
    - Los Angeles Repulses the Un-Americans, June 1955; 4.
  - District 10 Newspaper Clippings, 1938, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - "The Goose That Laid Our Golden Egg", January 3, 1938; 1.
    - "UE Leader Denounces U.S. Blacklist", October 1, 1948; 2.
  - District 10 Leaflets, 1938, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - "An Invitation" Regarding Utility Workers Organizing Committee and Southern California Gas Organization, March 17, 1938; 1.
    - "Let's Go" Regarding Organization, March 18, 1938; 2.
    - "GE Employees" Regarding GE Ontario Organization, May 5, 1938; 3.
    - "Convention Call", October 9, 1947; 4.
    - "Unity" Regarding Westinghouse Sunnydale and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, July 24, 1947; 5.
  - District 10 Press Release Regarding Deportations, October 14, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - District 10 Apex Organization, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Roscoe Williams to UE, May 16, 1937; 1.
    - Julius Emspak to Roscoe Williams, May 22, 1937; 2.
  - District 10 Western Electric Seattle Organization, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Richard Francis to James Carey, April 9, 1937; 1.
    - Francis to Julius Emspak, May 20, 1937; 2.
    - Emspak to Francis, May 26, 1937; 3.
    - Francis to Emspak, June 23, 1937; 4.
  - District 10 Pacific Gas & Electric Organization, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Albert Stonkus to Vic Levitt, October 27, 1937; 1.
    - Richard Prosser to Editors Regarding Press Release, December 1, 1937; 2.
  - District 10 Los Angeles Sub-District Council, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Ozro Sanders to Al Stonkus, November 27, 1937; 1.
    - Stonkus to Sanders, November 29, 1937; 2.
    - Ways and Means Committee to UE, December 3, 1937; 3.
    - Minutes, December 8, 1937; 4.
    - Vernon Kennedy to Utilities Division with Charles Shevlin Letter to UE Convention and December 8, 1937, Guy Wadsworth to UE Local 1414, December 9, 1937; 5.
    - Minutes, December 15, 1937; 6.
    - Minutes, December 29, 1937; 7.
    - Vernon Kennedy to Municipal Bureau of Water and Power, 1937; 8.
    - Minutes, January 5, 1938; 9.
  - District 10 Los Angeles Sub-District Council, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Minutes, January 12, 1938; 1.
    - Minutes, January 19, 1938; 2.
    - Vernon Kennedy Report, January 24, 1938; 3.
    - Minutes, February 2, 1938; 4.
    - Minutes, February 9, 1938; 5.
    - Minutes, March 14, 1938; 6.
    - Minutes, March 18, 1938; 7.
    - Minutes, March 23, 1938; 8.
  - District 10 Audit, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - John McDonald to C.H. Jordan with Balance Sheet, July 1, 1937; 1.
    - McDonald to Jordan with Statement of Account, July 6, 1937; 2.
    - McDonald to Robert Shippey, November 25, 1937; 3.
    - McDonald to Shippey, December 28, 1937; 4.
    - McDonald to UE, January 17, 1938; 5.
  - District 10 Tacoma Organization, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Freeman Cochran to UE, January 14, 1938; 1.
    - Julius Emspak to Cochran, January 21, 1938; 2.
  - District 10 Joint Council Utility Workers Organizing Committee, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Harry Bullock to Julius Emspak, March 28, 1938; 1.
    - Bullock to James Matles, March 31, 1938; 2.
    - Matles to Bullock, April 5, 1938; 3.
    - Emspak to Bullock, April 5, 1938; 4.
    - Bullock to Emspak, April 13, 1938; 5.
    - Vernon Kennedy to Emspak, April 14, 1938; 6.
    - Kennedy to Emspak, April 14, 1938; 7.
    - Kennedy to Emspak, April 15, 1938; 8.
    - Emspak to Bullock, April 18, 1938; 9.
    - Kennedy to Emspak, April 20, 1938; 10.
    - Joint Council Minutes with Leaflets, April 20, 1938; 11.
    - Emspak to Kennedy, April 21, 1938; 12.
    - Kennedy to Joint Council, April 21, 1938; 13.
    - Kennedy to Emspak, April 22, 1938; 14.
  - District 10 Joint Council Utility Workers Organizing Committee, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - William Mitchell to Vernon Kennedy, April 25, 1938; 1.
    - James Matles to Helio Kennedy, April 26, 1938; 2.
    - M.J. Sands to John L. Lewis, April 27, 1938; 3.
    - Minutes, May 4, 1938; 4.
    - Helio Kennedy to Matles, April 30, 1938; 5.
    - Emspak to Vernon Kennedy, May 9, 1938; 6.
    - Vernon Kennedy to Emspak, May 12, 1938; 7.
    - Vernon Kennedy to Emspak, May 13, 1938; 8.
    - Vernon Kennedy to Emspak, May 14, 1938; 9.
    - Emspak to Vernon Kennedy, May 18, 1938; 10.
    - Emspak to Kennedy, May 23, 1938; 11.
    - Vernon Kennedy to Emspak, May 24, 1938; 12.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, June 1, 1938; 13.
    - Vernon Kennedy to Emspak, June 4, 1938; 14.
    - Emspak to Vernon Kennedy, June 6, 1938; 15.
    - Vernon Kennedy to Emspak, June 13, 1938; 16.
    - Minutes, June 15, 1938; 17.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, July 11, 1938; 18.
    - Vernon Kennedy to Emspak, July 19, 1938; 19.
    - Helio Kennedy to Matles, July 27, 1938; 20.
    - Minutes, August 10, 1938; 21.
  - District 10 Joint Council Utility Workers Organizing Committee, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Helio Kennedy to Julius Emspak, August 11, 1938; 1.
    - Helio Kennedy to UE, August 11, 1938; 2.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, August 12, 1938; 3.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, August 14, 1938; 4.
    - Emspak to Helio Kennedy, August 18, 1938; 5.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, August 23, 1938; 6.
    - Robert Ontell to Los Angeles Trade Union Conference, August 25, 1938; 7.
    - Vernon Kennedy to UE, August 25, 1938; 8.
    - Minutes, September 7, 1938; 9.
    - Minutes, September 21, 1938; 10.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, September 22, 1938; 11.
    - Minutes, October 5, 1938; 12.
    - Helio Kennedy to James Matles, October 11, 1938; 13.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, October 12, 1938; 14.
    - Helio Kennedy to Emspak, October 14, 1938; 15.
    - Matles to Helio Kennedy, October 18, 1938; 16.